A Guide to the Governor James Barbour Executive Papers, 1812-1814
Library of Virginia
Arrangement
Arranged chronologically by date of document with pardons and undated items arranged to the rear.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Bibliography
Flournoy, H. W., CALENDAR OF VIRGINIA STATE PAPERS, January 1, 1808-December 31, 1835, VOL. X, Richmond: James E. Goode, Printer, 1892.
Contents List
- James Barbour Executive Papers
- 1812
  - January
    - 4-15 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 16-31 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - February
    - 1-15 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 16-29 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - March
    - 1-10 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 11-20 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 21-31 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - April
    - 1-15 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 16-24 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 25-30 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - May
    - 1-8 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - 9-15 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - 16-25 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - 26-31 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - June
    - 1-5 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - 6-12 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - 13-20 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - 21-25 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - 26-30 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - July
    - 1-6 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - 7-14 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 15-24 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - 25-31 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - August
    - 1-10 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - 11-20 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - 21-31 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - September
    - 1-10 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - 11-20 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - 21-30 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - October
    - 1-10 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - 11-20 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - 21-30 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - November
    - 2-14 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - 16-31 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - December
    - 1-15 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - 16-31 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Pardons
    - A-M (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - N-W (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
- 1813
  - January
    - 1-15 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - 16-31 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - February
    - 1-10 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - 11-15 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - 16-28 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - March
    - 1-7 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - 8-12 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - 13-16 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - 17-20 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - 21-25 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - 26-29 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - 30-31 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - April
    - 1-5 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - 6-9 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - 10-14 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - 15-21 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - 22-27 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - 28-30 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - May
    - 1-10 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - 11-15 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - 16-25 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - 26-30 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - June
    - 1-8 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - 9-15 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - 16-20 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - 21-26 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - 27-29 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - 30 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - July
    - 1-3 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 4-7 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - 8-10 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - 11-13 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - 14-17 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - 18-21 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - 22-29 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - 30-31 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - August
    - 1-10 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - 11-20 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - 21-31 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - September
    - 1-8 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - 9-19 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - 20-30 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - October
    - 1-10 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - 11-20 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - 20-31 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - November
    - 1-10 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - 11-20 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - 21-30 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - December
    - 1-10 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - 11-20 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - 21-31 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Pardons
    - A-H (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - M-W (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
- 1814
  - January
    - 1-15 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - 16-25 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - 26-31 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - February
    - 1-10 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - 11-20 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - 21-28 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - March
    - 1-10 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - 11-20 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - 21-31 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - April
    - 1-10 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - 11-20 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - 21-30 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - May
    - 1-10 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - 11-20 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - 21-31 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - June
    - 1-10 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - 11-20 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - 21-26 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - 27-30 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - July
    - 1-9 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - 11-15 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - 16-20 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - 21-27 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - 28-31 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - August
    - 1-10 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - 11-20 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - 21-28 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - 29-31 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - September
    - 1-5 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - 6-15 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - 16-25 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - 26-30 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - October
    - 1-10 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - 11-20 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - 21-31 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - November
    - 1-10 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - 11-18 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - 19-30 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - December
    - 1-10 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Filing Jackets (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Pardons
    - A-G (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - H-M (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - P-W (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Undated
  - Part 1 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Part 2 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Oversized (Clamshell Box)
  - 1812
    - Jan. 14 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Jan. 23 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Jan. [N.D.] (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Feb. 1 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Feb. 14 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - March 26 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - March [N.D.] (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - April 8 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - April 30 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - April [N.D.] (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - June [N.D.] (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - July 3 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - July 31 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Aug. [N.D.] (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Sept. [N.D.] (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Oct. [N.D.] (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Oct. [N.D.] (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Nov. [N.D.] (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Dec. 5 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Dec. [N.D.] (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Pardons - Amy (slave) (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - 1813
    - Jan. 4 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Jan. 10 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Jan. 12 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Jan. 18 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Jan. [N.D.] (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Feb. 12 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Feb. [N.D.] (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - March 26 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - May [N.D.] (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - June 12 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - June 23 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - June [N.D.] (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - July [N.D.] (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Aug. [N.D.] (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Sept. 9 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Nov. [N.D.] (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Dec. 16 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - 1814
    - Jan. [N.D.] (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Feb. [N.D.] (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - April 18 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - May [N.D.] (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - July 8 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - July [N.D.] (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Aug. 6 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Aug. 22 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Aug. [N.D.] (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Sept. [N.D.] (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Nov. [N.D.] (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Pardons
      - Dyer, William (Box 16, Folder 50)
      - Vaughan, James (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Undated (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Undated (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Undated (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Undated (Box 16, Folder 55)
- Oversized (Newspaper Box)
  - 1812
    - Feb. 25 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - April 15 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - April 21 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - May 12 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - June 25 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - July 1 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Oct. 26 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Dec. 17 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - 1813
    - Feb. 16 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - March 15 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - April 8 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - July 1 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - July 12 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - July 26 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Aug. 10 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Aug. 25 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Oct. 14 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - 1814
    - April 12 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - April 13 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - May 24 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - July 2 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Aug. 20 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Sept. 9 (Box 17, Folder 24)